The sky is shining in the dark
The sun is shining in the dark
You put your reflection on it
Only way makes you think about it
We're gonna train ourselves for a time
Of course, as always, I'll be with you
When you姐 the color was added, 같은 of the mood
Like that, I will forget that as I am, you are so strong
The time when I was young was a bit too long
The moment I saw you, I was so happy
You and you, you and you
If you want to be a star, I'll be able to be a star
I can't believe it, I can't believe it
Don't worry
It's time to say one last thing
We should go back home
You don't know where this is
And you don't know where my hands are
You're not scared
The family of adult Kyoguru and the others will be our big fun together
Let's go to the 3rd floor!
Everyone!
Yay!
Let's go to the 3rd floor!
It's delicious!
I'm going to the 3rd floor!
The 3rd floor is so good!
I got used to it!
Ok, this is a lot of fun.
Aaa!
There, there, there!
That's it, don't go!
Baby!
We are also waiting for the應 to have the delivery, so let's do it!
I've come to help you!
But, why are you hiding something like that?
There, there, there, there!
What?
Weeba, let's kick the bird!
Hey, guys!
Over there!
What are you doing here?
What are you waiting for?
I'm waiting for you!
Wait!
I won't let you in!
What is it?
Is it your turn again?
What do you mean by that?
So this is the place of Ranga-san!
Ranga-san's place?
Who decided this?
Ranga-san!
This place is the first place I've ever met.
It's the best place I've ever met.
I won't let you in!
You're really a lucky guy.
What do you mean?
I've never thought about it before.
You've never thought about it?
If I were you, I'd have to go back to the world.
What would I do with you?
If I weren't here...
I wouldn't have thought about it.
How do you know where to go?
I can think of a way to go back.
It's a blessing.
I can think of something.
I can think of Ranga.
I'm going to be a young man who's going to be a great man.
I'm going to be a great man.
I told you.
I'm going to be a great man who's going to be a great man.
If I were you, I'd have to become a real man.
I'm going to be a great man!
Be honest.
We've lost on these nomads today.
Because we have elected to do our best to make them pay us.
The best?
Of course it is.
Someone is taking responsibility.
I love that sort of thing.
I wish not only of nomads here but I stays amidst the gonna.
I'm not thinkin' that kind of a gentle girl.
We'll go on.
A delicious meal!
New year's day!
Channel's day!
Start! Start!
I can't get in here!
Is that equal to the three?
Who! I can't get in!
I'm not doing a move!
This is also not good!
Who was there?
Yes, it's too bad!
That's not it! That's not it!
I'm just a kid!
Here we go!
Where do you want to go to?
I'm full of chocolates!
No!
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Dad, I'm too busy with the store.
I'm too busy.
I was so busy that I was busy with the store.
What? You're too busy, aren't you?
But I'm not that busy with this store.
I don't think we can go anywhere else.
Yeah.
That's right!
You're so mean!
You're always being so mean.
That's why I'm always being so mean.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
You're always being so mean.
What's with the difference?
The End
I'll make a huge step in the next step!
What is that?
I'll take care of the money.
I'll take care of the food and make it for my own sake.
That's right, it's a labor business.
I'll take care of the necessary ingredients.
Then, let's take a lot of time to get a drink.
We'll have to take a lot of time to get a drink.
Great! We're the lucky ones! Let's do our best, Lanka!
I've been riding this for years.
What's the matter with you, Oro?
I heard that you're going to get a drink.
You're going to be fine.
Well, I don't know what to say, but I don't want to say anything about it.
What about the meaning?
It's important to decide what to do in the world of jungle.
It's not like that.
Well, I'll listen to it one more time,
but if I can't go back to the world with the most important thing,
what should I do?
What should I do?
I don't think so, so I can't answer.
It's not like I'm talking about a bad thing, but I'm not talking about it, so please forgive me.
I'm not afraid!
I don't want to do anything!
Did you say something?
If you can't go back to the world, this is the only way.
I won't let you go.
You don't have to be a bad person, right?
Don't eat that!
I'm not afraid!
Are you afraid?
That's the only way I can find the truth.
That's right, but...
The vegetables are good for the hobby, so I'll help you.
What to do?
What?
Did you say that I made a mistake?
Darn it!
The vegetables areNg and they are all spoiled.
Let's go now.
Food is delicious, huh?
keeping is also worth it, you know.
All the antebrates are doomed with acumen.
What do you mean by abusing the appetite?
Wait, the meat was so tender, I can see the cooking.
Are you still going? I'm sorry, but I don't feel good.
Even if it's not for food, it's good to have delicious food here, so I'm relieved.
Well, calm down when you're like this.
Of course, you have to look for the way to eat.
I don't want to eat.
There's nothing wrong with the food I just ate right now.
It's okay, it's okay.
The food is very crispy on the outside.
What are you doing, Noto?
I'm the boss of the friend of the house, and you're the boss.
The boss?
That's because of the food I just ate.
It's because of the food I just ate.
Why are you laughing?
Anyway, I can make it a day or day.
It's all right.
Come on!
No! This is so bad!
I have to go home, and I'm starting!
I don't need to see you, do you understand?
Thank you for everything!
It's an ordinary farewell!
You're right!
It's a friendship between us and the nation!
Thank you!!
You are the one who has to make a toast to us!
Thank you!
This is a rare thing.
I was surprised to see the nature of the island until now.
So I can show you how to open it in the middle of this hole.
This place is not even opened yet.
It's hard to find a place to hide the food in the middle of the hole.
Ah!
I've been waiting for a long time.
You've been waiting for a long time to go to Tokyo!
I've been waiting for a long time to go to Tokyo!
This is it?
It looks cute, but you don't have to worry about it.
I want to tell you something, right?
You'll regret it!
I can't do anything about it.
I wonder if this will continue for a day?
It's not necessary to set the order that you're taking.
It's strange.
It seems that it's good to see it in the eyes.
It's all over here.
I don't have anything to do with Tomoroko or Jagai.
What's wrong with you?
I can't stand it until I finish my work.
What are you talking about?
Hi, Papa.
Are you going to wake up?
You're going to wake me up, right?
What's wrong?
Mr. Hagen!
Did you catch a fish?
I don't want to catch a fish.
This is the first time I've ever caught a fish.
I don't want to do this, but my mom...
We...
I don't want to do this.
Really?
What?
Mr. Kojo, are you okay?
I'm not worried.
I'm going to catch a fish.
Mr. Kitsutsuki and other people?
I'm looking for food.
It's a fish.
I told you it was delicious.
What's going on?
I'm not worried about the fish.
It's a fish.
What's wrong with you?
Mr. Kitsutsuki, what's wrong with you?
I'm going to catch a fish.
It's a fish.
I don't know what to do.
What?
That's right.
There's a lot of fish here.
I can't find any fish.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
I can't find any fish.
I'll go get it.
This world was completely destroyed.
It looks like the entire island was destroyed.
I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on.
What's wrong with Kyu?
It's a bit strange.
I see.
It's a bit strange?
That's right.
It's like Kyu Ryuu-san's.
It's a bit strange.
I see.
Kyu Ryuu-san, we're always together.
We always had to go to the island when we were together.
That's right.
Tsujiu Chahashi
We're heading towards Kyogi.
Let's get on with it.
Tosuma, come on!
Get off!
We can't do it!
I'm not going to lose the game.
Why don't you take it?
Damage, what kind of a game is this?
What will happen to Moria and this world?
I don't think that's the right thing to do.
Moria...
Look...
What shall we do?
Marく...
Look...
Ouch!
You're coming?
No!
No...
Look...
N-No, it's not.
So it's a miracle that I caught a fish,
and I was able to hit this fish all of a sudden,
and got close to my mouth.
I'm ashamed of this.
That's why I'm asking you.
I'm begging you to stop!
Hey!
The rest will be brand new.
Got it?
Got it!
That one...
Okay!
It's fresh!
It's the most delicious.
Tasty!
This is Megumi's taste.
It's an amazing soup, isn't it?
Even if you open your eyes, it's already 10 minutes.
I want you to open your eyes like Kyoryu-san's, so that everyone can open their eyes like that.
Oteinpa! Oteinpa, are you there?
I don't want to make anything anymore.
I think about the future, too.
I love this place so much, so I'm taking it seriously.
It's so delicious!
It's so delicious that you can open it like that.
I love this place so much, so I'm taking it seriously.
It's so delicious!
Please go to the bathroom!
I'm going to the bathroom.
I always have a bed.
We'll be in line.
I'll be able to see the star in your eyes.
My heart sings.
I like this place so much, so I'm taking it seriously.
It's so cool.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to get rid of those memories.
Unfortunately,
the father and father were in the same place.
If the father was in the same place as the father,
the father would be in the same place as the father.
Yeah!
I was sad to say that I was a demon.
I was the one who was born and the one who was born.
The inside of that being is...
N-Nant!
M-M-YAH!
Next time, I'll be on the other side of the world.
I'll be on the other side of the world,
and I'll be on the other side of the world, M-YAH!